Father,
I wish to confess.
You wish to confess.
I saved you.
I saved this city
and all your worthless lives.
I should have let Stannis kill you all.
Here I am.
[Applause]
Do you wish to confess?
Yes, father. I'm guilty.
Guilty? Is that what you want to hear?
You admit you poisoned the king. No, of
that I'm innocent. I'm guilty of a far
more monstrous crime. I'm guilty of
being a dwarf.
You are not on trial for being a dwarf.
Oh, yes I am. I've been on trial for
that my entire life.
Have you nothing to say in your defense?
Nothing but this.
I did not do it.
I did not kill Joffrey, but I wish that
I had. Watching your vicious bastard die
gave me more relief than a thousand
lying
I wish I was the monster you think I am.
I wish I had enough poison for the whole
pack of you. I would gladly give my life
to watch you all swallow it.
Samaran escort the prisoner back to his
cell.
I will not give my life for Joffrey's
murder. And I know I'll get no justice
here. So, I will let the gods decide my
fate.
I demand a trial by combat.
[Music]
[Applause]
Heat.
[Music]