mr zane you scheduled this hearing we've
been waiting 10 minutes i'm not waiting
any longer
well uh you don't have to your honor my
motion is here
better get up here fast
where the hell were you i'm standing up
here with my dick in my hand and you're
out having a soda
i had something to do yeah well whatever
it was i hope it's worth almost losing
this case over
motion expedite trial i thought this was
a hearing on their motion to dismiss
well if you expedite our trial that
takes care of their motion to dismiss
your honor they just got this case two
days ago they're using the timing of our
clients contract exploration to try to
shake us down
i have to say mr zane i find it hard to
believe that in two days you found out
enough to know you need an expedited
trial let alone
care about these people at all your
honor four years ago a mail carrier
named stanley powell felt tightness in
his chest
he thought it was nothing but his wife
insisted he go to the hospital
when he got there doctors couldn't find
anything wrong but they wanted to keep
him for one
extra day now unfortunately
kelton insurance refused to pay so mr
powell went home
crawled into bed and one day later he
was dead in front of you you have a
complaint that's over 5000 pages long
which tells the stories of another 189
victims
pick a page at random tell me the number
and i will tell you
exactly what their client did to them
your honor are you actually buying that
page 627 mr
lawrence greene 63 year old grandfather
admitted to saint vincent with
complaints of lower back pain and
excessive weight loss
he thought it was stress turns out it
was lymphoma
only they didn't find out until it was
too late because their client refused to
pay for the mri
so please rule against us if you have to
but don't tell me we don't care motion
for expedited trial granted
jury selection starts monday
for your information that's what i was
doing and it only took as long as it did
because i was also doing something for
the one person who has the right to
treat me like his associate
but treats me like his partner anyway
well if you can forgive me
would you say i take my partner out to
[Music]
lunch
you