I just wish Tommy was here.
[Music]
I'm telling you now, we got lost. I
can't really need to do a map. I mean,
[Music]
[Applause]
my boys are all here
today.
This is my [ __ ] wedding day.
Yeah. And you said there'd be no bloody
uniforms.
Neverless. Nevertheless, John, despite
the bad blood, I'll have none of it on
my carpet. Now, for Grace's sake,
nothing will go wrong. Those bastards
out there and her family. And if you
[ __ ] do anything to embarrass her,
your kin, your cousins, your horses,
your [ __ ] kids, you do anything to
what?
What about Sn?
Yeah, they're women of sports. I'll say
that.
No. No, no,
no cocaine.
No cocaine, no sports, no selling
fortunes, no racing, no [ __ ] sucking
petrol out of their [ __ ] cars.
And you, Charlie, stop spinning your
arms about me, eh?
Oh, I'm just trying to sell you to them,
Tom.
But the main thing is you bunch of
[ __ ] despite the provocation from the
cavalry. No fighting.
No fighting. No [ __ ] fighting. No
fighting.
No [ __ ] fighting.
Good.
Get the