don't answer that
[Music]
question oh
[ __ ] we ran well over a
mile I object to these two get
married we we uh we we're past that part already  what are my options then how about leaving you
shut the hell up you satanic hose bag hey  Gerald I'm sorry it sounded so harsh but
you'll understand why he said that in a few  minutes ain't going to be a few minutes you
goddamn son CM down calm down let the boy talk  I can't let you marry this chick I can't believe
you're doing this listen to me buddy you don't  love this girl I'm telling you I had love it's
different it's a different feeling love is like  it just leads you to a special connection it's
it's full of like feelings of of Awesomeness and  and and and the feelings you you you that wrap
around you it's it's it's it's deep in your  stomach it's in your head it's in your [ __ ]
nutshack it's in your di when it gets hot still  love it to tip and it [ __ ] sprinkles out like
morning to shooting all over the grass okay I've  had just about enough of this Phil sit down before
I tell your wife what you did to the strip club  okay son I'm sorry I just I can't let you marry
this skank Son Your Son Well what if what is he  talking about honey you can tell me I'll forgive
you that's what Love's about right forgiveness  all right fine Donnie's not my best friend he's
my father my parents didn't die in an explosion I  lied because I'm the product of an inappropriate
teacher student relationship teacher student  relationship do you know how gross that sounds
you're disgusting are you [ __ ] kidding me right  now she can still cancel that check Donnie should
cancel what check I don't she gave me 50 Grand  to keep my mouth shut 50 Grand Jamie yeah uh
it was uh I was going to hold on to it you know  to get me out of jail but yeah yeah that's what
I think it is that's how much I hate this [ __ ]  [ __ ] wait wait keep your mouth shut about what
Don don't listen to him he's a liar and he's  crazy father MN please continue I promise to
do all that [ __ ] you mentioned and so does  Todd right wait what is going on tell him no
no no no no no no don't tell don't tell him you  tell him or I'll tell everybody here it's up to
you come
on oh okay well that's not that bad what  you didn't tell him you [ __ ] lion piece of
[ __ ] get on it now or I'll [ __ ] Crush you  Jame you can tell me I mean how bad could it
be
what okay she told him
what you [ __ ] your brother  oh my God [ __ ] white
people I'm not looking so bad now am I
[Music]
dad