last ready to make my fortune my  first day as a future master of the
universe
They called it Black Monday no [__]. By  4 p.m, the market had dropped 508 points.
The biggest plummet since the crash of 29.
I know  your family you know mine no I don't know some [__] country in Europe took a [__] let them do  what they want to [__] do our market sounds solid
Do not answer the phone a lot of people are going  to be calling you trying to get your dirty laundry.
You don't know what's going on here. i know, i know
Holy
[__] [__]
Unbelievable. My first shitty day is a broker.
Within a month LR Rothschild,  an institution since 1899 closed its doors.
Wall Street had swallowed  me up and [__] me right back out again
wake up on my