this contitution is nothing but a
license for oil companies and foreign
interest to destroy my beloved W wadia
will remain a
dictatorship W or be quiet why are you
guys so anti- dictators imagine if
America was a dictatorship
you could let 1% of the people have all
the nation's wealth you could help your
rich friends get richer by cutting their
taxes and bailing them out when they
Gamble and lose you could ignore the
needs of the poor for health care and
education your media would appear free
but would secretly be controlled by one
person and his family you could wire to
phones you could torture foreign
prisoners you could have rigged
elections you could lie about why you go
to war you could fill your prisons with
one particular racial group and no one
would complain you could use the media
to scare the people into supporting
policies that are against their
interests I know this is hard for you
Americans to imagine but please try I
will tell you what democracy is
democracy is the worst andless talking
and listening to every stupid opinion
and everybody's vote counts no matter
how crippled or black or female they are
[Music]
democracy democracy